Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Light Creation Magic! Light Swords of Conviction!
Copy Light Magic! Light Swords of Conviction!
Mono Zone! Spirits hush dead!
Again!
I don't know if it's a magic stone or not, but that belongs to me. Give it back!
Nice job, Ronay!
And now, we can finally make things right.
Indeed.
I can tell when someone's lying.
And I wonder why you told a lie just now, Ronay.
What's going on?
Who the hell are you?
Don't tell me. This reincarnation, it can't be.
Don't be mysterious!
Did you say your hair or God?
What's that?
Looking for, Ronay?
Oh God!
Blast!
You've got u.
Be it.
You didn't want to pick, 진!
A holy bress count!
You're not months to make things right, t-o of it.
It's, yeah.
You've got characters and想 mysteries at Hornay.
Love!
Tell me!
Putち果てた世界で
負けられる戦いたち
びっくりするグラカフェ
エロな、ノーノー
負けるわけないじゃん
誰もなく続く
省略創造以上
気を振りかかせた敵
自分の心をまだ見ぬあてるに
もういいじゃん
ちょっとじゃん
やられたらやり返す
そういう言葉
止まんない衝動
とんでもなれやむ
いらないんでしょう
分かり合えない場所を
やり切るまで
染められ勝てろ
切り切る
全てなくなるまでやるよ
ドバイバイ
To be continued...
No matter how many lies I had to tell, I wanted to see him one last time. That was my disloyalty.
And for that transgression, I earned a giant hole in my chest. But still, what in the world is this wretched thing that created the hole in the first place?
That thing is the biggest liar of all. How long has it been posing as Rone? How long has it blended in with us?
No!
Raya! Raya! What's the meaning of this, Rone?
The three leaves of the clover. They represent integrity, hope, and love. Within a fourth leaf dwells good luck. And within a fifth, there resides a devil.
That reminds me of the day I took advantage of two mages chosen by four-leaf grimoires and used their pain to create a grimoire of despair.
Now I can finally obtain what should have been mine all along.
This magic, it doesn't belong to an elf.
Here in the Shadow Palace, a place that lies between this world and the next, I can use this to bring me what I want out of the land of the dead.
At long last, I have returned.
Rone, Rone, no!
What is this? A pitch-black magic? And why is it so cold?
Don't tell me. Is he…
The devil?
This creature… What is he?
Though it's still incomplete, it's been centuries since I've been in my own body. And it's such a wonderful feeling.
You've used your four-leaf grimoire well, elf. I commend you. I praise you from the bottom of my black heart for all that you've done up to this moment and the results you've shown me.
And now, you shall taste the depths of despair, just as another did all those centuries ago.
Another? But who? What is going on here?
That day, the one who tricked the humans into betraying the elves was none other than… why me, of course?
They were so easy to manipulate. Humans will do anything for power.
Let's foster understanding.
And then you lot made it even easier, letting me trick you in the most amusing way.
The revenge went exactly as planned.
I might have known. You're nothing but a bunch of fools.
How dare you!
Return.
Hey! That body belongs to Captain Vongeance. Your carelessness will get him killed.
I'll deal with you later. I have things to do.
I don't think so. You'll deal with me now. Whatever kind of monster you may be, I won't let you have your way. If all I have to do to end this nightmare is destroy you, then so be it.
Monozone! Spirit storm!
Vacuum barrier.
What?
All your attacks are meaningless in the face of my word-soul magic.
Word-soul magic? His power is insane. And now that I'm stronger, I understand. I can't beat this guy. Well, I can't do it alone at least.
Ahhhhhhhh! You know!
How about time, Asta.
Hold on a second. What's happening? What is that strange creature?
Whoa, freaky! What the heck is that thing down there?
Wait. I have a weird feeling that I should know the answer.
No, some uninvited guests have crashed my party, but I suppose they can stay.
More importantly...
Approach me now, elf.
Word soul magic, which means everything he says becomes reality.
Could that also be what he used to recreate Rooney's switching magic while posing as him?
That's enough!
Light creation magic, light whip of...
Vanish!
Iron lances!
Pondry?
Asta! That creepy horned monster is behind all of this!
I got it!
Tempest of Blades!
I can get rid of these easy!
Some of them are physical weapons!
My anti-magic can't erase those!
Dammit!
It's all I can do just to evade them!
Vacuum barrier!
Be crushed to dust!
Smashed to powder!
Broken to bits!
Riddled with holes!
Asta!
You know!
I won't let anyone stand in my way!
Asta!
You know!
I won't let anyone stand in my way!
Are you still awake?
I must thank you!
As a direct result of your efforts, time will start moving for me again!
Without you, we wouldn't be here now, hero!
Five centuries ago, they got in my way!
And though I came close, my incarnation failed!
What are you saying?
Rather than admit defeat, I selected you to be my next unwitting pawn!
A new sacrifice, loved by mana, still young and oh so easily swayed.
Tragedy, a sense of purpose, a mission to fulfill.
That's all it took to turn you to forbidden magic that would reincarnate the Elves' souls in human form!
No, you have it wrong.
Not me.
Licht was the one who reincarnated us in human bodies.
It's true he dealt into forbidden magic, but he did it for us.
He gave us a chance.
You're incorrect!
Truth is, he had nothing to do with your reincarnation.
Only, I'm afraid.
Ugh.
You don't understand your leader's wishes. He doesn't want to exterminate humanity. The restoration of the Elves, the revenge you so longed for. False goals, all of them. You merely followed the path that I laid for you, and led the other fools along the way.
You did a truly splendid job.
I couldn't have asked for a more useful tool.
And in the end, it brought about a future Licht would never want.
I don't believe it.
And my incarnation, allowing my soul to return to my body at last.
It's not true.
He's lying.
I'm like him.
I am just like Licht.
The four-leafed clover chose me.
Well, you were chosen, that's true.
But not by the four-leafed clover.
By me, my little puppet!
Excellent work.
What the hell is this creature of darkness? And is it saying that it used Licht in the same way that Licht used all of us?
All of us?
Audrey, I'm sorry. Everything that we had accomplished.
It's so amusing. Elves and humans so alike. Your dreams and ambitions make the most excellent playthings for creatures like me.
I've heard enough!
You think you can just show up out of nowhere and make a mess of things?
Okay, sure. You're super strong and scary, I'll give you that.
But who do you think you are?
Whatever you are, it pisses me off!
You're nothing but an ugly, stupid piece of trash!
And I won't lose my dream because of you!
I knew it! They're okay!
The magic that's welling up from within him, it's transforming the objects near him into wind.
Could it really be true? Could Licht's child be waking up within him?
Oh? His anti-magic is overflowing, erasing all magic in his vicinity.
Is it possible it's resonating with my own? How very remarkable!
Tempest of Blades!
The Blades!
Asta?
Yes!
Yuno's taking care of the physical blades while Asta deals with the magical wounds!
They're combining their powers to block them all!
Together you and I can feed him!
If you're going to stand in our way, then we will break you down!
Heal injury.
Damn it! What is going on here?
He can heal himself?
You wounded me, I'm impressed.
You possess the power of a spirit in our beloved Vain Mana, and you the power of a meddlesome comrade dwelling within the five leaf grimoire that should have belonged to me.
I don't know where you came from, comrade, but it does not matter. You may have that grimoire.
When the owner of a four leaf grimoire is engulfed in deep despair, a miracle happens! A five leaf grimoire is born out of the darkness within!
At last! I enjoy both my precious body and my pitch black grimoire!
Now I can rule this world, a devil in possession of my true form and full power!
Five hundred years ago, I successfully manifested a grimoire of despair, but ultimately, I was met with resistance.
That won't happen again, though.
This time, I used reincarnation magic to sow seeds of wicked thoughts in their very souls, making them far easier to corrupt.
I needed my stepping stones to do their job, to allow themselves to be stepped on.
I needed them!
Empty hearts are so simple and predictable!
All for the sake of this moment, I have deceived, killed, and plundered!
It was a delight!
You monster!
I'll make you pay! You'll never get away with this!
Unfortunately for you, I'm not the one you have to deal with. Sorry!
Rampage as you please. Allow your fear and despair to be your guides.
No! No!
The final form of an elf overflowing with malice!
A dark elf!
Demon-like magic! Light swords of conviction!
No! No!
The final form of an elf overflowing with malice!
A dark elf!
Demon-like magic! Light swords of conviction!
Black light! And it moves so fast! Even with monosone, I couldn't evade it all!
Asta! You still alive?
Of course I am! Who do you think you're talking to?!
That was a crazy number of swords! And they came at us so fast!
If my anti-magic hadn't softened the blow, I'd be totally dead right now!
Not good. He's gotten even stronger than before!
The destined one who carries the hybrid child of the elves and the humans, and the other who lacks magic but is still able to handle the five-leaf grimoire!
They'll both meet their end in this fight. I'm not sure who you are, Devil, but if you don't steal that body soon, you will die along with it!
I'm confused! I don't feel any key coming from him at all!
Perhaps because this is a heartless, burned-out shell, merely casting scorched shadows of the spells from its grimoire!
But you might as well try to have some fun with it!
So the exit's about.
Now then, if you'll excuse me, I must bid you farewell!
Where do you think you're going?!
Is he still breathing.
Not that.
Well, if I won, don't quite, don't move!
Something speak really more Μ Emmanuel from the nine years old…
Then just help us keep breaking enough.
Let the Christians win you and the most likely you don't have to hall out the enemy of evil temets?
The teacherASX is just a copy of the wheater and the character A ECM exam?
Kill!
Oh no!
Ji-
Ah!
Ahhhh!
Judo!
Mana-zone?
Spirit Storm!
I wish you'd stop.
I doubt you can forgive me since I'm a human.
And I can't forgive you either.
But still, I know this!
We should've been able to understand each other!
I'm begging you, please stop!
Hatred.
Oh no!
This spell!
What truly multiplied to the sky?
Oh no!
This wordategory is broken down into the mountains You wouldn't want to see.
싶은 dachte There too!
Oh no!
Thank you.
笑うのも痛い でも本当は強くないよ 歩くべき道をずっと手探りだけで探してる
No matter what's happened in the past
No matter what hardships and pain we've been through
I know we can understand each other
Next time on Black Clover, page 116
The ultimate natural enemy
I am never going to give up
We can see what happens in the past
And now we can see what happens in the past
I am never going to give up
No matter what happens
I'm not going to give up
But if there's no pain in the past